(忆往昔)
那是什么
So, what is it? What? What? What?
鬼魂  恶魔  还是什么
Spirit, demon, what?
我不知道
I don't know.
-是什么  -我不知道
- What is it? - I don't know.
是粘液  没错
Oh, yeah, we're goo positive.
什么意思  什么意思
What does that mean? What does that mean?
这不是精确科学
It's not like it's an exact science.
老弟  搞什么鬼
Dude, what the hell?
我不知道
I don't know.
说正经的  到底搞什么鬼
No, seriously, what the hell?
我不知道
I don't know.
随便说点什么也好
One theory, any theory.
-你是谁  -我叫科尔
- Who are you? - Name's Cole.
我两次派驻伊拉克  特种部队  去过达尔富尔
I did two tours in Iraq. Special ops, Darfur...
你哥哥迪恩
And your older brother, Dean...
他在哪
Where is he?!
他和我  是老相识了
...He and I, we go way back.
我的工作  就是猎杀怪物
What I do... is hunt monsters.
你有家人  科尔
You've got a family, Cole.
我想他们需要你回去
I'm guessing they need you to come back,
他们需要你完完整整地回去
and they need you to come back whole.
爸爸
Dad!
迪恩·温彻斯特杀了我爸爸
Dean Winchester murdered my father.
那不是你父亲  科尔
That was not your father, Cole.
你爸爸是怪物
Your dad was a monster.
他是什么怪物
What kind of monster was he?
我不知道
I don't know.
从没见过那种  之后也没再见过
Never seen that kind before, never seen it again.
(如今)
(北卡罗来纳州   费耶特维尔)
[邪恶力量 第10季第15集]
(该隐血印)
看啊
Hey, check it out.
看黄片呢
Porn?
什么  才不是  没什么的
What? No. I-it's nothing.
我不会说你什么的
Hey, look, no judgement from me.
但是别在吃饭的地方看啊
Just, you know, not where we eat.
哥们  不是黄片啦
Dude, it wasn't porn.
色情刊物  随便啦
Okay, "erotica." whatever.
裤链拉好  看这个
Zip it up. Check this out.
(二等兵尸体被发现)
被害人受过近身格斗和柔道的训练
The vic was trained in krav maga and jiu-jitsu.
还是被放了血
Still ended up with her organs drained,
而且骨髓完全被吸干净了
and the marrow was sucked completely out of the bones.
那就是食人了
So...cannibalism.
食人怪吗
You thinking a rugaru?
或是神祇
Or a god, maybe.
我去把西装翻出来
I'll go dig up my pencil-neck suit.
等等  什么
Wait, wait, wait. W-what?
这对你还不够诡异吗
What, is this not weird enough for you?
是挺诡异的
Well, yeah, it's weird, but, um, I mean, we... we...
但是...
I mean...
那好  10分钟后车里见
Great. 10 minutes. I'll meet you in the car.
好吧
Great.
(该隐血印)
萨姆
Sam.
我知道你在看什么  不是黄片
I know what you're doing over there, and it ain't porn.
伙计  我们什么网站都看遍了
Look, man, we have checked every website, okay?
看两遍了
We've checked it twice.
萨姆  我们办案子的时候
Sammy, when we work a case,
到了一定时候
there's always that... that point...
我们就得面对现实
when we have to face the truth, right?
即便我们不喜欢这种现实
Even if we don't like it.
现实就是
Well, truth is...
这东西没得逃避
There's no way around this.
我们看到了该隐的下场
We saw what happened to Cain, okay?
我也不喜欢  但我得继续生活
I'm not happy about it. But I got to move on.
所以我要继续做我们该做的
So I'm gonna keep doing what we do...
直到我做不了了
while I still can.
我希望你能陪着我
And I'd like you to be there with me.
(费耶特维尔除虫)
好了
All right.
(费耶特维尔市政厅)
是联邦探员吧
Agents, I gather.
是从衣服看出来的
Uh, was it the suits,
还是我们有股联调局的臭味儿
or do we give off some sort of a Fed stench?
是衣服
I-it's the suits.
二位有什么需要
What can I do for you boys?
我们是前来调查
Well, uh, we are here investigating
二等兵杰姬·普莱斯科特之死的
the death of private Jacki Prescott.
该死  你们专程从华盛顿赶来的吗
Shoot. You drove all the way down from D.C.?
是啊
Yeah, we did.
那抱歉浪费你们时间了  探员们
Well, then sorry to waste your time, agents,
但这案子已经结了
but we wrapped that one up.
犯案的是个特种部队军官
Guy that did it was a special forces officer...
里克·威利斯
Rick Willis.
你为什么确定是他
What makes you so sure it was him?
仓库里到处是他的指纹
His fingerprints were all over the storage room
他在基地一间仓库里动的手
out on the base where he did it.
甚至把狗牌留在了尸体旁边
He even left his dog tags by the body.
他被关押了吗
So, is he in custody?
没有  那混蛋喝下一大桶汽油
No, bastard drank a boatload of gasoline,
自焚了
then lit himself on fire.
这么死可够惨烈的
Well, that's a hell of a way to go.
可不是  留下个妻子和幼儿
No kidding. Left a wife and a baby.
六个月来第三起自杀了
Third suicide we seen in six months.
军事小镇啊
Military town.
要来点蛋糕吗
Would you like some cake?
-好啊  -算了  不用了
- Yeah. - No, uh, y-you know what? Uh, we're okay.
很好吃的  我搭档做的
No, it's really good. My partner made it.
看上去很棒  不过我们不用了
It looks great, but we're... no, we're all right.
但我们还有个问题
Uh, we do have one more question.
尸体上有咬痕吗
Were there any bite marks found on the body?
没有  凶器是猎刀
No. Vic was killed with a bowie.
警长  多谢配合了
Well, sheriff, thank you for your time.
嗯
Yeah.
没有咬痕  那么不是食人怪了
No bite marks. That rules out rugaru.
那是神祇吗
So what? A god?
这可不妙
I don't like the sound of that.
那家伙自焚了
The guy molotov-cocktailed himself.
简直疯了
That's bonkers.
像是被恶魔附体了一样
That's like demon-possession bonkers.
是里克干的
Rick did it.
我没想狡辩
I'm not trying to say that he didn't.
但是
But...
他刚刚派驻归来
I mean, he just got back from deployment,
我们都知道那对士兵能造成什么样的影响
and we've all seen what it can do to a soldier's mind.
我的里克
My Rick...
他回到家  精神很好的时候
...when he's home and good...
蜘蛛都得靠我打
I have to kill the spiders, you know?
里克很善良
Rick was a kind soul.
他从未杀过不该杀的生命
He never took more life than he had to.
你之前有没有注意到什么奇怪之处
Did you, um, notice anything strange, weird,
比如情绪暴躁
like, uh... violent mood swings?
或者怪味儿
Or weird smells?
没有  但是
No. But...
里克...很...
...Rick was... he was so...
他很渴
He was thirsty.
渴什么
Thirsty for what?
水
Water.
他会把大半天花在用花园水管喝水上
He'd spend half the day drinking from the garden hose.
后来  还有一晚  我发现他在浴缸里
And then, one night, I caught him in the tub
喝洗澡水
drinking the bathwater.
我叫他停下
When I told him to stop,
他简直像听不到
it was like he couldn't even hear me.
而且他的皮肤干燥很严重  都流血了
And his skin, it got so dry it bled.
他去见医生了吗
Did he see a doctor?
我带他去了退伍军人协会
I took him to the V.A.,
但他却只能一等再等
but he just got on a list to get on a list.
后来他不再说话了
And then, he stopped talking...
他已经完全失常了
and just wasn't himself.
我还以为是创伤后应激障碍
I thought maybe it was PTSD.
请节哀
Uh, we're very sorry.
你说里克刚从派驻归来
You said that Rick was recently deployed.
知道他被派驻去哪了吗
Do you have any idea where?
不知道  那都是机密
No, that stuff is classified.
妻子都不能知道
They don't even let the wives in on it.
好吧
Right.
那我们
Okay, well, we'll, um...
我们不打扰了  如果你想到了什么
We'll leave you alone now, but if something comes up,
任何东西  请打给我们
anything at all, just give us a call.
还有件事
There's one other thing.
我在超市碰到了朋友杰玛
I ran into my friend Jemma at the supermarket.
她嫁给了基特·维森  里克的队友
She's married to Kit Verson, a guy from Rick's team.
她觉得基特这次回来也变了
She thinks Kit came back different this time.
我觉得我们似乎遇到了一样的问题
Kind of felt like we were dealing with the same thing.
谢谢
Thank you.
基特的确有些烦恼
Kit's been going through some stuff for sure.
恢复正常
Um, you know, it takes him a while
-是需要时间的  他总能恢复  -谢谢
- to get back to normal, but he always does. - Thanks.
你呢  你怎么样
And what about you? How are you holding up?
我没事
I'm okay...
基本没事吧
for the most part.
因为里克和贝丝的事
You know, what happened to Rick and Beth, it...
让人很难过
It's been hard.
多亏上帝仁慈啊
"There but for the grace of god," you know?
可以跟你丈夫谈谈吗
May we speak with your husband?
他昨晚出去了
He, um... he went out last night,
他应该就回来了
but he should be back any minute.
基特派驻归来之后
You know, Kit, he comes back from these deployments,
总是需要空间
and he needs his space.
他出去了一整晚吗
So he's been out all night?
是的
Well...yeah.
天呐
God.
我都骗不了自己
I can't even convince myself.
我好担心
I'm worried.
这不像他
This isn't like him.
他最近很渴吗
Has he been thirsty,
会跟狗抢水那么渴
like "drink out of the dog bowl" thirsty?
你怎么知道
How did you know?
认出了你的车
Recognized your wheels.
你怎么来了
What the hell are you doing here?
杰玛打给了我
Jemma called me in.
我还是新兵蛋子时就认识基特了
I've known Kit since we were military brats
在同一个基地待过
raisin' hell on the same base.
他是个好人
He's a good man.
没人说他不是
Well, no one's saying he's not.
是吗
Oh, really, now?
那么你们是冲着杰玛的茶来的吗
So, what are you two, uh, here for, Jemma's sweet tea?
要告诉我你们究竟为什么而来吗
You want to tell me why you're really here?
我们在查案子
We're working a case.
基特的案子吗
Oh, Kit's case?
老实说  我们还不能确定
Honestly, we're not sure just yet,
但看上去是这么回事
but, um, it's looking like it.
你是这么说
Says you.
镇上发生了一起谋杀-自杀案
There's a murder-suicide in town.
你朋友基特跟凶手是队友
Your buddy Kit? Same unit as the killer.
而且有同样的怪毛病
Same whacked-out antics.
所以
So...
我们不会离开的
Look, we're not going anywhere, all right?
如果你在乎你朋友
And if you care about your buddy,
就让我们来处理
you'll let us handle this.
我还是跟你们来吧
Nah, I think I'm gonna be coming with you.
想得美
Oh, the hell you are.
我认识人  我能帮忙
I got contacts. I can help.
你帮不上的
You really can't.
比如  我有个朋友是军队情报机构的
For example, a friend of mine works military intelligence...
还欠我个人情
owes me a favor.
他会知道里克和基特执行了什么任务吗
Would he know what Rick and Kit's mission was?
当然  而且他会告诉我的
Sure. And he'd tell me all about it.
好吧
Okay, fine.
不好
No, it ain't.
我能猜到是怎么回事
You know, I figure what's going on here...
我要死死跟着你们
I stick to you two like flies on roadkill,
确保我朋友能完好无损地回家
make sure my buddy comes home in one piece.
我知道你们在想什么
Look, I know what you two are thinking,
但我们不能猎杀我的好哥们
but we are not gonna hunt my best friend,
他还是个战争英雄呢
who happens to be a frigging war hero, by the way.
我们要找到他
We are gonna find him.
这是有区别的
And that's the difference.
伙计  我们也知道
Hey, man, we're right there with you, okay?
-基特是个英雄  -但你得做好准备
- Kit's a hero, but... - But you got to prepare yourself.
基特可以已经不是自己了
Kit might not be Kit anymore.
先生
Uh, sir?
先生  你得先付钱
Sir, you have to pay for that first!
瞧你干的好事
Now, look what you ma--
有个家伙闯了进来  快回商店来
This guy just came in. Get to the store, man.
快点啊
You got to hurry.
给
Here you go.
食物来了
Sustenance.
我查不到牛死亡
Listen, I got nothing on cattle deaths,
或是诡异天气  什么都没有
freakish weather... none of it.
那或许不是恶魔
So... probably not a demon.
或许根本不是你们那种案子
So maybe it's just not your kind of thing at all.
化疑虑为食欲
Well, when in doubt...eat.
来了
Okay, here we go.
(发送者  未知  查看)
(加密邮件)
我收到一封军队情报机构那个朋友发来的密信
I got an encrypted e-mail here from my friend at the M.I.
怎么说
And?
这个嘛
Well...
基特和里克被派去营救一名美国战俘
Kit and Rick were sent to rescue an American P.O.W.
他被关押在伊拉克纳贾夫公墓
being held in Iraq... the Najaf cemetery.
公墓
Cemetery?
那些混蛋把那里当做监狱用
Bastards use 'em as a, uh... as a prison.
这里有一段视频  是威利斯头盔摄像头拍的
I got some footage here from the camera on Willis' helmet
他跟基特执行的最后一桩任务
during his last mission with Kit.
好了  上
Okay, go!
趴下
Down. Get down.
安全
Clear.
琼斯少校
Major Jones?!
马特·琼斯少校
Major Matt Jones?
-那边  -琼斯少校  是你吗
- Hey, right here. - Hey, major Jones, is that you?
我是基特·维森上尉
Hey, I'm captain Kit Verson.
我们来救你回家了
We're here to bring you home, man.
搞什么啊
Oh, what the hell?!
他搞什么啊
What the hell was that?!
我猜结局很不堪吧
I'm guessing that didn't have a happy ending.
是啊  任务失败了
No, it did not. Mission failed.
战俘被警卫射杀了
And that P.O.W. got shot by guards.
是吗  就是这样吗
Really? That's what happened?
官方是这么说的
That's the official story.
基特和里克回来都有问题
All right, so, Kit and Rick came back screwed-up.
这我们是知道的
We know that much.
里克发了疯
Well, and then Rick jumped the high dive.
天呐  基特
God, Kit.
怎么了
What was that?
我设置手机接收本地警报
I set my phone to get local alerts.
情况不妙吗
Is it bad?
很血腥
It's bloody.
好吧  我们走
All right, let's get out of here.
他舔了地板上的血
He licked the blood off the floor?
那个汽水小哥似乎吓得不轻
Yeah, the soda jockey back there seemed pretty shook up by it.
他给出的描述  中等身材  棕色头发
Now, the description he gave... medium build, brown hair...
听上去像是基特吗
That sound like the Kit you know?
-是的  -好
- Yeah, it does. - Great.
还觉得不像我们那种案子吗
So still sound like it ain't our kind of thing?
杰玛
Hey, Jem.
科尔  新闻上说有人被杀了
Cole, uh, the news said someone was killed
在肯顿街的加油站
at the gas 'n sip on Kenton.
我知道  我在这里呢
Yeah, I know. I'm here right now.
是吗
You are?
他们怎么说
W-what are they saying?
没什么消息  杰玛
Not much. Look, Jem.
我现在没法多说  抱歉
Um, I really can't talk right now. I'm sorry.
等等
Wait.
他们认为是...基特
Do they think that he... that... that Kit...
干的吗
did this?
我不知道
I don't know.
如果是他  他现在不正常
If he did, he isn't in his right mind,
你知道的  科尔
and you know that, Cole.
你得救他
You got to save him.
我会的
I will.
我知道
I know. And, uh...
这是现在唯一让我不至于发疯的了
And that's the only thing keeping me sane right now.
我在想  有时候
I was thinking, you know, sometimes,
基特想单独待着时
when Kit wanted to be alone,
他会去北边  他父亲的老木屋住
he would head up north to his dad's old cabin.
或许你可以去看看
Maybe you could go check it out,
我待在家  以防他回来
and... and... and I'll stay here in case he comes home.
好
Right.
功夫小子  来不
Hey, kung-fu grip, you coming?
杰玛  我得挂了
Hey, Jem, I got to go.
我们去哪
So, what next?
去10英里范围内的每一家警局
We hit every cop shop within a 10-mile radius,
到处问问  看能不能找到他
put the word out, see if we can't track him down.
如果你们找到了他呢
And if you find him, what then?
基特需要帮助
Kit needs help.
不是吃枪子  不是挨刀子
He doesn't need a bullet, and he doesn't need a knife.
好吧  科尔
Okay. You know what, cole?
我们知道你想保护你朋友  但是...
We know you want to protect your buddy, but...
如果他成了怪物  我们只能干掉他
If he's a monster... we got to put him down.
只能如此  是吗
That's the way it's gonna have to be, huh?
职责所在
That's the job.
你加不加入
So, you in or out?
多谢送我一程
Thanks for the lift.
这样也好
It's better this way, all right?
你安抚住她  我们有消息告诉你
You keep her calm. We'll keep you posted.
嗯
Yeah.
科尔
Hey, Cole.
他如果出现了  别逞英雄
He shows up, don't try and be a hero.
给我们打电话
Call us.
明白
You got it.
亏你还给他买了晚餐
And you bought him dinner.
基特
Kit?
基特  你在吗
Hey, kit? Are you here?
我是科尔啊
It's Cole.
有几个很厉害的角色在找你  基特
There's some real serious people looking for you, Kit.
他们可不仅仅是想找你谈谈
And they won't just want to talk.
情况很糟糕  基特
It's bad, Kit.
你要么面对我...
And it's either me...
不然就得面对他们了
or them.
基特
Hey, Kit.
我很抱歉  我停不下来
I'm sorry. I can't stop.
等一下  等一下
Wait, wait, wait!
天呐
Oh, god.
有东西...我咽下去个什么东西
Something went down my...throat.
好了  科尔  试着镇定下来
All right, cole, just try and stay calm.
-天呐  -科尔
- Oh, god. - Cole?
那东西在动  它是活的  萨姆
Something moved. It's alive, Sammy.
好吧  我们会把它弄出来的
All right, well, we're gonna get it out of you, okay?
-怎么弄  -我们会找到办法的
- How?! - We'll figure it out.
伙计  你单枪匹马来这里真是太蠢了
Man, that was a dumbass move coming here alone.
你知道吧
You know that, right?
我很抱歉  我本该让"砍刀兄弟"
Oh, I'm sorry. I should have let the machete brothers
来把我朋友的头砍掉的
cut my buddy's head off.
假如你真让我们那么做了
Well, if you did,
你现在也不会咽下去一只肉虫王了
maybe you wouldn't be choking down a damn khan worm right now.
肉虫王是什么
What's a khan worm?
你觉得是那玩意吗
You think that's what it is?
或者是它的变种亲戚
Or some sort of freak cousin.
什么东西的变种亲戚
Freak cousin of what?
几年前  迪恩和我办过一起案子
A couple years back, Dean and I worked a case.
我们和这种虫子一起被困在一个罐头厂里(S06E16)
We got stuck in a cannery with this worm.
它会钻进人的身体然后...
It would get into people's bodies and --
这虫子可讨厌了
It was freaking awful.
好吧  那你们以前遇到过这种情况
All right, so you've been to this rodeo before.
我们要怎么杀死它
How do we kill it?
最坏的情况  得把虫子的宿主爆头
Worst case -- headshot the person it's in.
然后虫子就会爬出来
Worm crawls out,
我们一脚踩死它
we stomp it like a bug.
有没有一种办法是你不爆我头的
Is there a version where you don't cap me?
有的  上一次
Yeah, uh, last time,
电击迫使这虫子离开了人体
electrocution made the worm leave the body.
好吧  就电击吧  我奉陪
All right, fine. Electrocution it is. I'm game.
好吧  你俩开工吧
All right. You two get to work.
我去找基特
I'll go look for Kit.
-萨姆  -怎么了
- Hey, hey, Sammy? - Yeah.
假如能把我治好  那基特也有救  是吧
If we can fix me, we can save Kit, right?
没错
That's the idea.
你知道这会疼得你哭爹喊娘吧
You know that this is gonna hurt like a son of a bitch?
靠  我有妻有子
Hell, I have a wife, a kid,
还有乱七八糟的按揭要管
and an upside-down mortgage to get back to.
不惜一切代价  迪恩
Whatever it takes, Dean-o.
好吧
Okay.
上一次你遇见这玩意
So, last time you saw this thing,
它也是把普通人变成了杀人狂吗
It turned people into killers, too?
是的  只不过那一只还控制了我们的思想
Yeah, except that one did a mind-control number on us.
我去
Damn.
日复一日
Day in, day out,
你和萨姆
you and Sammy
拯救人们免受灵异事物的侵害
saving people from things they just can't wrap their minds around...
甚至都没人知道
Hell, and nobody even notices it.
至少我做的贡献还能赢个奖章
Hell, at least I get a medal for my efforts.
但是你...
But you...
我还试图杀死你
I tried to kill your ass.
是啊  真愉快
Yeah. Well, good times.
我差点就把你干掉了
I almost took you off the map.
那现在还有谁能来救我呢
Who would be saving me now?
是啊  我们还是别整的这么煽情
Yeah, well, let's not get too sentimental about it.
好了  我们把这东西发动起来吧
All right, let's fire this puppy up.
你说的好像这不过是普通的一天
Well, you say that like it's just another Tuesday.
老兄  今天才周一
Oh, buddy, it's only Monday.
有东西出来吗
Anything?
上一次  它是从我们耳朵里出来的
Last time, it came out of our ears.
怎么样
And...?
我还没看见有东西出来
I'm not seeing anything yet.
再来一次
Do it again.
好了  那混蛋这会儿该爬出来了
All right, that sucker should have crawled out by now.
再来
Again.
我继续的话  会害死你的
I keep going, this is gonna kill you.
再来
Again!
科尔
Cole.
科尔  别这样  别这样
Cole! Come on. Come on.
科尔
Cole!
好了
Okay!
好了  再来一次
All right. Again.
不行
No.
不行  我们不能再玩"手术游戏"了
No, we're done playing "Operation."
我再电你  你就要被电死了
I zap you again, you're toast.
休息下吧
Just take a knee.
迪恩
Dean.
-怎么样了  -虫子没出来
- How did it go? - Worm was a no-show.
这不科学啊  上次...
That doesn't make any sense. Last time --
这次是这次
Well, this ain't the last time.
也许这是一种全新的物种
I mean, maybe this is a whole new species, you know?
我只知道电击是不行了
All I know is that sparky struck out.
一定有办法的
Well, there's got to be something.
万物都有弱点  不是吗
I mean, everything has a weakness, right?
那你呢  有什么发现吗
Well, what about you? Any luck?
我正要去基特家
I'm on my way to Kit's.
我觉得应该先去那查查
Thought I'd check there first.
好的  抓紧了  伙计
All right, well... hurry up, man.
明白
You got it.
你还好吗
You okay?
力不从心就是这样吗
So this is what in over your head looks like.
保持注意力就好
Just got to keep your head in the game.
好吧  关于这玩意儿我们知道什么
Okay, what do we know about this thing?
它会吸走你体内的水分
Uh, sucker dries you out.
我现在已经口干舌躁了
I'm thirsty already, man.
它喜欢水
It likes water.
当水无法满足它
Then when that's not enough...
就是血  我也不清楚
Blood. I don't know.
缺水或许会让这东西暴躁
Maybe lack of fluids makes the thing hostile.
就和寄生虫一样
So it's like a parasite.
吸干你的水分  然后寻找下一个寄主
It wrings you dry, and then it moves on.
那如果我让自己脱水
So if I dry myself out,
这鬼东西就不那么喜欢我了  是吧
the son of a bitch wouldn't like that very much, now, would he?
对  它就会想出来了
No, he'd want the hell out.
你就是恶劣环境了
You'd be a hostile environment --
不过你这人一直都凶巴巴的
well, more than you already are.
不能这么说  你没见过我和气时的样子
Well, to be fair, you really haven't seen my chiller side.
你觉得快速脱水怎么样
What do you think about rapid dehydration?
爱死了
Big fan.
它出来以后  你可别放过它
Just make sure you squash that sucker when it goes awol.
这计划不错
Sounds like a plan.
好了
All right.
林中蒸汗屋最棒了  是吧
Nothing like a sweat lodge in the woods, huh?
基特
Kit?
亲爱的
Honey.
看着我
Look at me.
你怎么了
What's happened to you?
听我说
Listen.
无论发生了什么  无论你...
Whatever happened, whatever you...
干了什么
you did...
我们都能解决  好吗
We're gonna fix this, okay?
我们能把你治好的
We're gonna get you well.
亲爱的
Baby.
基特
Kit!
基特  停下  求你了
Kit, stop! Please!
我停不下来
I can't...stop.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
没事
Yeah.
你们搞起了蒸汗
You're in a... sweat lodge?
是你说的  任何东西都有弱点
Well, you're the one who said everything has got a weakness.
出点汗  如果能杀了这玩意
So I figure take a schvitz, kill a freak.
那也算不错了
Call that a good day.
如果能奏效的话
Yeah, if it works.
你有更好的主意吗
Well, you got a better idea?
还真有  迪恩
Yeah, I do, actually, Dean.
我们知道如何结束这一切
We know how to end this.
我知道  B计划就是杀
Yeah, plan "B" For "bullet."
但我们现在还不能放弃  你先撑住
But we're not quite there yet, so just hold tight.
好
All right.
他妻子怎么样
How's the wife?
她快崩溃了  科尔呢
She's barely holding on. How's Cole?
他很坚强
He's going strong.
很好
Good.
迪恩  基特快醒了
Look, Dean, Kit is gonna come to.
我赶到的时候  他的情况已经很糟了
And when I got here, it was bad.
时间紧迫  我明白
We're on the clock. I get it.
好
Yeah.
接着流汗  伙计  你做得不错
Just keep sweating, man. You're doing great.
对不起了
Sorry.
我不明白
I don't understand.
基特最后一次和里克一起执行的任务
On Kit's last mission, on his deployment with Rick,
出了意外
there was an incident,
有东西进入了基特的体内
and something got inside Kit.
你看到什么了吗
I mean, h-have you seen anything?
我看到了
I mean, y-- I saw something, okay?
但那...
But it -- it was...
那是怪物
It was a monster.
真真切切  活生生的怪物
It was a real-life, actual, honest-to-god monster.
你丈夫...
And your husband...
被它改变了
...it changed him.
什么
What?
你究竟是什么人
Who are you?
我爸爸也是被什么东西控制了  是吧
My dad...he got something inside him, too, right?
他转化时  也是如此吗
You think this is what he felt like when he turned?
也许吧
Maybe.
但变成怪物前  他也曾是人
I mean, he was human before he was... a monster.
我明白
I get it...
你为什么那么做了  迪恩
why you did it, dean.
他当时已经不再是我爸爸了
My dad wasn't my dad anymore.
如果我和他一样
If I go down that same road...
我希望你也能一样对我
I want you to do that to me, too.
和他一样
That road?
那就是放弃
That means giving up.
如果你觉得你也会那样
If you think that's where you're headed,
那你是想反了
then you've got it ass-backwards.
你得用尽全部的力量去反抗
You're gonna fight harder than you ever have.
明白了吗
You understand?
迪恩
Dean-o.
你能不能把我绑在这椅子上
Will you do me the honor of tying me to this chair?
好
Yeah.
得了  我们都知道你不会下手的
Come on. We both know you're not gonna do it.
你得坚持到底
You are gonna sweat this one through.
我做不到  迪恩
I can't, Dean!
你可以的
Yes, you can.
听我说  你可以的
Listen to me. Yes, you can.
想想你的家人
Think about your family, hmm?
你的妻子  孩子  听到我说的了吗
Your wife, your kid. You hear me?
谢谢你的鼓励  教练
I appreciate the talk, coach.
但说实话  我满脑子
But honestly, all I can think about
就只有割开你的手腕  痛饮你的血
is slicing your wrist and drinking you like a fountain.
这就意味着我是个怪物  是吗
I guess that makes me a monster, don't it?
你是猎人
So, you're a hunter.
-对  -然后
- Right. - And...
抱歉  我得花点时间消化
I'm sorry. This is gonna take me a minute.
这...
It's, uh...
很疯狂  对吗  听起来很疯狂  我知道
It's crazy, right? It sounds crazy? I know.
但这就是真相
But it's the truth.
我不在乎他是否
I don't care if he's
是你说的那样  好吗
what you say he is, okay?
他是我老公
He's my husband.
杰玛  他试图杀了你
Jemma, he tried to kill you.
你看着他双眼时  看到的还是你老公吗
Was that your husband when you looked into his eyes?
还是你认识的基特吗
Was that the Kit you know?
听着  迪恩在努力解决
Look...Dean is working on it.
迪恩和科尔会弄明白的  好吗
Dean and Cole will figure it out, okay?
我打电话确认一下
Let me check in with them.
好吧
All right.
萨姆  萨姆
Sam. Sam.
萨姆
Sam.
快点  萨姆  接电话啊
Come on, Sammy! Pick up!
别逼我扣扳机
Don't make me pull this trigger.
我已经做到了
I already did.
见鬼
Holy...
你还好吗
You okay?
是的  谢天谢地
Yeah. Oh, thank god.
谢天谢地
Thank god.
萨姆  我们成功了  科尔没事了
Sammy, we did it. Cole's all right.
快点把基特送过来
Get Kit over here as soon as you can.
太晚了
It's too late.
科尔
Hey, Cole.
听着  我...
Listen, uh, I, uh...
不管怎样
For whatever it's worth...
我真希望结果不是这样
I really wish it hadn't ended this way.
嗯  我也是  萨姆
Yeah, me, too, Sammy boy.
基特  他当时想杀了她
I mean, Kit -- he was gonna kill her and --
我知道  杰玛都告诉我了
I know. Jemma told me everything.
士兵发了疯  攻击了他老婆
Solider goes crazy, attacks his wife.
她不得不杀了他
She had to kill him.
至少这是她得说出去的故事
Or at least that's the story that she's got to tell.
我想我现在都见识到了
I guess I've seen it all now.
一部分  不是全部
Some. Not all.
我只想回家  见我的家人
I just want to go home, see my family.
我想感谢你  迪恩  谢谢你救我
I want to thank you, Dean-o, for keeping me standing.
只需要一点血一点汗  再多点汗
Well, all it took was a little blood, sweat, and, uh, more sweat.
照顾好自己  听到了吗
You take care of yourself, you hear?
好的  我会的
All right, I will.
但我还是希望以后再也不用见到你俩
But I still hope I don't see the two of you anymore.
无意冒犯
No offense.
没关系
None taken.
别为基特的事责怪自己
Don't blame yourself for Kit, man.
我忍不住  迪恩  感觉糟透了
I can't help it, Dean. It feels crappy.
我知道
I know it does.
我尽力了  真的
I tried. I did.
我尽力了  只是...
I tried. I just...
我没法救他
I couldn't save this one.
有时候  你什么都做对了
You know, you can do everything right.
但是...
And even still, sometimes...
那人还是救不成
The guy still dies.